okay yeah so as introduced on my hacker
好的，是我的骇客介绍的
typesafe which means I work on the
类型安全，这意味着我在
occult orchid and I've been also part of
神秘兰花，我也参加过
the reactive streams let's call it
反应性流我们称之为
movement or committee which has been
运动或委员会
developing a specification and they test
制定规范并进行测试
kit for interrupt of different stream
用于中断不同流的套件
implementations other than that yeah
除此之外的实现
bunch of other open source stuff such as
一堆其他开源的东西，例如
aj MH performance benchmarking plugin
aj MH性能基准测试插件
for now sbd yeah other one that's a
现在sbd是的，另一个是
bunch of community things and
一堆社区的东西和
conferences I Ron you might have heard
我可能已经听过罗恩的会议
of seen them but this is not very
见过他们，但这不是很
important today today let's focus on
今天很重要今天让我们专注于
code so the plan for today is first to
代码，因此今天的计划是第一个
actually introduced water if dreams are
如果有梦想，实际上会引入水
perhaps not everyone is yet familiar
也许不是每个人都熟悉
with them so we'll talk about the
与他们，所以我们将谈论
concepts and what the specification
概念和规格
actually means and why we need it and
实际上意味着，为什么我们需要它，以及
then a little bit how it actually works
然后一点点它实际上是如何工作的
so how it really works behind the scenes
所以它在幕后的真正运作方式
to van jump in to occur streams which is
范跳进来发生流是
one of the implementations of this
此的实现之一
specification but it actually provides a
规范，但实际上提供了
useful API you can really work with a
您可以真正使用的有用的API
new stuff because the rectus dreams API
新事物，因为直肌梦想着API
is a very very very low level and you
是一个非常非常非常低的水平，你
wouldn't get much done with you will
不会为您做很多事情
just restraint the vcp ice now so
现在就限制vcp冰吧
there's going to be a bunch of concepts
会有很多概念
of ARCA streams a few examples and when
的ARCA流的一些示例以及何时
I have a bunch of code prepared and
我准备了很多代码，
might I de so we can jump into some
我可以，所以我们可以跳入一些
hacking at the end yeah I said before
最终入侵，是的，我之前说过
all questions and answers type them into
所有问题和答案将其键入
the questions pane and then we'll go
问题窗格，然后我们去
over a few it first some questions are
首先是一些问题
outstanding i'm happy to follow up over
杰出的，我很乐意跟进
email so we'll see how that goes so what
电子邮件，所以我们将看看情况如何
is a stream so in general this first
是一个流，所以一般来说这是第一个
nice definition that you cannot enter
您无法输入的好定义
the same river twice let's help hello
同一条河两次让我们打招呼
Cletus so ancient Greece what it
Cletus那么古希腊么
actually fits very well so the general
实际上非常合适，所以一般
idea is um but if you work with streams
想法是嗯，但是如果您使用流
if you look at the same stream twice you
如果您两次看相同的视频，
may get different data right because
可能会获得正确的数据，因为
it's this flowing stream of data and
就是这种流动的数据流，
you're just observing a part of it this
你只是在观察其中的一部分
of course depends on the type of stream
当然取决于流的类型
because there may be streams which are
因为可能有一些流
backed by a collection right and if you
有收藏权的支持，如果您
observe a stream from a collection you
观察您收藏中的信息流
may always get the same elements right
可能总是正确地获得相同的元素
because the stream always always
因为流总是总是
materializes from the first and goes to
从一开始就实现
the last element of a collection but you
集合的最后一个元素，但是你
cannot always do that right if you read
如果您阅读不总是能做到这一点
from a socket for example or I don't
从插座，例如，或者我不
know watch a live video stream and you
知道观看直播视频流，您
don't buffer stuff you may not be able
不要缓冲您可能无法使用的内容
to go to the beginning of time to see
去时间的开始看
stuff it's a live stream most of the
大部分时间都是直播
time so let's talk about reactive
时间，让我们谈谈反应式
streams reactor is a big word of course
溪流反应堆当然是一个好词
recently all over the media and Internet
最近遍及媒体和互联网
but what do we actually mean when we say
但是当我们说时我们实际上是什么意思
work live streams because it's a very
工作直播，因为这是一个非常
precise definition at least in the
至少在
specifications that so of course we're
我们当然是这样的规格
talking about stream processing so some
谈论流处理
number of elements will be going over a
元素数量将超过
bunch of transformation steps and when
一堆转换步骤以及何时
you get the end result but now the key
您得到最终结果，但是现在关键
features coming so it has to be back
功能来了，所以必须回来
pressured by back pressure we mean for
受背压的压力
example if you are processing or
例如，如果您正在处理或
generating some a huge number of data
生成大量数据
and someone has to count a verte very
有人必须非常数一个
complex algorithm on top of the data
数据之上的复杂算法
perhaps that consumer of your data which
也许是您数据的使用者
is easy to produce is not able to keep
容易生产不能保持
up with processing this complex
处理这个复杂的问题
algorithm so this is where back pressure
算法，这就是背压的地方
comes in were of a subscriber the the
进来的是一个订户
receiver of this data is able to signal
该数据的接收者能够发出信号
to the publisher so the generator of his
给发布者，所以他的生成者
data but it can't keep up and we can do
数据，但跟不上我们可以做的
different stuff about that and it has to
关于它的不同的东西，它必须
be a synchronous well and doesn't really
成为同步井，并没有真正
have to because the specification is
必须因为规范是
broad enough to allow the synchronous
足够宽以允许同步
execution but it is really aimed for a
执行，但实际上是针对
synchronous and possibly even
同步甚至可能
distributed because it's
分布是因为
possible to implement this over the
可以通过
network and yeah processing so this
网络和处理是这样的
means for example in a car we have his
意味着例如在汽车中我们有他的
famous and mantra that never block and
永远不会阻止的著名和咒语
this of course plays very well with
这当然与
reactive streams because you never
反应性流，因为您从不
really have to block on I don't know
真的要封锁我不知道
some core because someone is taking your
一些核心，因为有人将您
own time to process and adamant instead
有自己的时间去处理，并坚持
you may be forced to be back crush it
你可能会被迫退缩
and stop producing things but it's not
停止生产东西，但这不是
the same as being blocked by some
就像被某些人封锁一样
blocking io core and then the key
阻塞io核心，然后是关键
feature of this thing is headed
这东西的特点
standardized so by standard as we mean
按照我们的意思标准化
with a number of implementations and
具有多种实现方式和
everybody about the same protocol so
每个人都使用相同的协议
here's a summary back dress at the
这是在
synchronous stream processing in a
同步流处理
standard if you want to read up on the
标准，如果你想阅读
standard and the technology
标准与技术
compatibility kit which I implemented
我实现的兼容性套件
the worst fear active streams web page
最担心的活动流网页
and versa yeah all the background behind
反之亦然，所有背后的背景
it so go ahead check it out okay but who
因此，请继续进行检查，但是谁
is actually running this now of course
实际上现在正在运行此
first us type safe but those other
首先，我们键入安全，但其他类型
companies behind it and backing it such
支持它的公司
as Netflix with 4rx libraries and show
Netflix，带有4rx库并显示
your photos and other companies such as
您的照片和其他公司，例如
pivotal and red cat with their
关键和红猫与他们
implementations of the same
相同的实现
specification and now to the to the key
规格，现在到关键
what this specification gives us so for
该规范为我们提供了什么
example if you have this pipeline where
例如，如果您有此管道，
different elements are erected streams
竖立不同的元素流
are X our car or reactor thanks to
X是我们的汽车还是反应堆，这要归功于
everybody abiding to the same protocol
每个人都遵循相同的协议
you are able to connect fees without any
您无需任何费用就能连接费用
kind of world hard work let's put it
辛苦的世界让我们说吧
this way because we all abide was in
这样，因为我们都遵守
protocol they are able to back pressure
他们能够背压的协议
from end to end so in this graph example
从头到尾，所以在此图示例中
reactors paper to back pressure the
反应堆纸背压
ecosystem the ecosystem convector Rick
生态系统生态系统对流瑞克
RX + RX can back pressure some reactive
RX + RX可以反压一些反应性
streams publishing so this is really
流发布，所以这真的
huge and one thing to notice that the
巨大的一件事要注意的是
API I'm gonna destroy the describe lot
我要销毁API的描述很多
now may not be the easiest to implement
现在可能不是最容易实现的
and in fact it's not really ain't that
实际上，那不是真的
everybody implementing their own
每个人都实现自己的
reactive streams fin it's more I'm dad
反应流越来越多，我是爸爸
if a database driver or I don't know a
如果是数据库驱动程序，或者我不知道
video processing library is able to
视频处理库能够
expose such interface most users will
暴露大多数用户会这样的界面
just use folks so it's for this interop
只是使用乡亲，所以这个互操作
but most of the time you won't be
但是大多数时候你不会
implementing those and directly you
实施这些，直接你
might be using alcohol too consumed with
可能使用的酒精与
our United using reacted seamless here I
我们的曼联在这里反应无缝
go I've got an example how this all fits
我有个例子
together so each line you can see here
在一起，所以每一行你都可以在这里看到
is actually a different reactive streams
实际上是不同的反应流
implementation all embedded in a red
实现全部嵌入红色
backward web server so you can see we
向后Web服务器，以便您可以看到我们
start with an RX observable then we go
从可观察到的RX开始，然后我们开始
over reactive streams into a aqua sauce
在反应流中变成水酱
which one maps in this bunch of numbers
哪个映射在这堆数字中
to a string and when we go over to
到一个字符串，当我们转到
reactor which does different thing and
反应器做不同的事情和
they all connect together and work
他们都在一起工作
together to produce will conduce the
一起生产将有助于
result so in essence we are trying to
结果，从本质上讲，我们试图
fight back login because I mean if you
反击登录，因为我的意思是如果你
can't connect one API to another API
无法将一个API连接到另一个API
this some form of locking move erect
这种形式的锁定动作直立
extremely api's we are able to open up
极端的API，我们能够打开
and use everybody's best features so
并使用每个人的最佳功能
let's broad overview about what it
让我们大致概述一下
actually is but what is this back
其实是，但是这又是什么
pressure thing and like I said we have a
压力的东西，就像我说的，我们有一个
situation where we have a publisher in a
我们有一个出版商的情况
subscriber and they talk to each other
订户，他们互相交谈
of course that's what we do and one
当然，这就是我们要做的事情之一
thing to notice is very are strictly
要注意的事情很严格
typed as in this publisher will be
在此发布者中输入
producing things of type T well it can
可以很好地生产T型物品
produce subtypes of T boots and get the
产生T型靴子的亚型并获得
idea which is different to our
与我们不同的想法
correctors which currently are untyped
当前未键入的校正器
but we are changing but also so the
但我们正在改变，但也如此
problem appears when you have a fast
斋戒时出现问题
publish on this flow subscriber right so
这样就在此流订阅者上发布
both have some rate of processing and in
两者都有一定的处理速度
this case when you have a first
这种情况下，当你第一次
publisher it would overwhelm the vessel
发布者，它将淹没船只
scriber
划线员
so while i do i need that protein let's
所以在我需要的时候，让我们
look at the typical example so the
看典型的例子
publisher tries to send some later of
发布商尝试稍后发送
course one way or another that's going
当然会以一种或另一种方式
to be some buffer space on the receiving
成为接收方的一些缓冲空间
end even if it's just a list of elements
即使只是元素列表也要结束
just a some kind of buffer or even the
只是某种缓冲，甚至
TCP buffer on a different system there
那里的其他系统上的TCP缓冲区
is some kind of buffer always and and we
总是某种缓冲，而我们
fill out foot buffer so what can happen
填写脚缓冲器，这样会发生什么
next the subscriber is not really able
接下来的订户不是真的能够
to process at the same rate as it's
以相同的速度处理
being given data so what's going to
被提供数据，那将如何
happen is we're going to overflow the
发生的是我们将要溢出
buffer so what do we do how do we handle
缓冲，所以我们该怎么办
buffer overflows where most of the time
大部分时间缓冲区溢出
and you will drop the messages because
您将删除邮件，因为
you do not have any space to fit for
您没有任何空间可容纳
messages and then the publisher would
消息，然后发布者会
have to resend or just leave live with
必须重新发送或只留下
the fact that you lost data but let's
事实上，您丢失了数据，但让我们
say we resent it it may seem a bit
说我们很讨厌，这似乎有点
costly that you just drop the data and
仅删除数据并
then you resend it but please keep in
然后您重新发送，但请继续
mind button I mean every TCP based
介意按钮我的意思是每个基于TCP的
system does exactly this if I TCP
如果我使用TCP，系统便会执行此操作
buffers for messages or packets in that
消息或数据包的缓冲区
case will be dropped on the floor and
案件将被丢弃在地板上，
will have to be recent so it's a valid
必须是最新的，这才是有效的
strategy but we can do better than that
策略，但我们可以做得更好
so a typical answer is yeah I can send a
所以典型的答案是，我可以发送
knack so sending a knack is when you
诀窍，因此当您发送诀窍时
notice that oh my god I'm gonna over
注意，天哪，我要结束了
from my buffer space so you notice this
从我的缓冲区空间中，所以您注意到了这一点
and you want to avoid early out of
而你想避免提早退出
memory error for example you can send a
内存错误，例如，您可以发送
Mac so next time for a negative
Mac，所以下回负面
acknowledgement and it works like this
确认，它像这样工作
and then we're going to talk about if
然后我们要讨论的是
it's enough or not so the subscriber
是否足够，所以订户
notices but it has not much space left
注意，但剩余空间不多
in its buffer and perhaps it is in
在它的缓冲区中，也许它在
danger of overflowing the buffer then it
缓冲区溢出的危险
concerned his orange arrow down on the
关注他的橙色箭头向下
bottom here it can send to the publisher
可以在此处发送给发布者
a synchronously a negative
同步否定
which would mean but hey dear publisher
这意味着但嘿亲爱的出版商
would you mind stop sending data for a
您介意停止发送数据
while and yea the a way behaved
而是的，一种行为方式
publisher will just stop sending data
发布者将停止发送数据
plan the only problem with that is that
计划唯一的问题是
it may not get fair in time so I noticed
时间可能不公平，所以我注意到
my buffer space is running out I send
我发送的缓冲区空间用完了
out the negative acknowledgement but in
否定承认，但在
the meantime because this is a is
同时，因为这是一个
entering the system there were some
进入系统有一些
messages in flight which ended up with
飞行中的消息最终以
overflowing the buffer anyway so this is
反正缓冲区溢出，所以这是
bad this obviously isn't safe but what
不好，这显然不安全，但是
happens if we have a slow publisher and
如果发布商的速度慢，并且
a fast subscriber let's talk about the
快速订阅者，我们来谈谈
inverse way of doing back pressure so
反方向做背压所以
the previous one is negative
前一个是负数
acknowledgement so if we can't keep up
致谢，如果我们跟不上
we say 'hey i can't get the other way is
我们说“嘿，我无法理解
pulling so every time i am ready to
拉，所以每次我准备
consume an element I tell the subscriber
消耗一个我告诉订户的元素
gave me an element but that doesn't
给了我一个元素，但是那没有
really scale in a situation where we
真正在我们遇到的情况下扩展
have a fast subscriber miss low
快速订阅者错过率低
publisher because there will be a lot of
发布商，因为将会有很多
spamming going on back in the opposite
垃圾邮件反过来
direction so the subscriber will keep
方向，以便订户将保持
telling the publisher that is ready to
告诉发布者已经准备好
consume data at the rate a hundred
以一百的速度消耗数据
thousand times more sometimes then the
有时是数千倍
data is able to be produced emitted so
能够发出数据
let's no good so the reactive streams
让我们不好，所以反应流
backpressure model is a combination of
背压模型是
those two models so we sometimes call it
这两个模型，所以我们有时称之为
dynamic push poor but effectively we
动态推动力差，但我们有效
have two observations here if we just
如果我们只是在这里有两个观察
use the push mother so the knack model
使用推母，所以诀窍模型
it is not safe right and we want our
这是不安全的权利，我们希望我们的
model to be safe if we just use pole and
如果我们只使用极点和
it's going to be too slow in the
它会太慢
opposite situation when the subscribers
订户时情况相反
actually fast so the solution is to
实际上很快，所以解决方案是
switch between V smells
在V味之间切换
but the switching can't really be an
但是切换不能真的是
explicit as in oh now I'm in push mode
像现在一样明确，现在我处于推送模式
ooh now an informal just to be voted
哦，现在只是一个非正式的投票
into the prodigal so here's Phil
进入浪子，这里是菲尔
reactive streams solution to back
反应流解决方案返回
pressure what it does is when you have a
压力是什么，当你有一个
slow subscriber at world and you have
世界上缓慢的订户，你有
any kind of subscriber it will tell it
任何类型的订户都会告诉它
to the publisher give me some data and
给出版商给我一些数据，
the sum is a concrete number will be
总和是一个具体数字
given the request message so i can say
给了请求消息，所以我可以说
request free which means i am ready to
请求免费，这意味着我准备好了
consume free messages this may seem very
消耗免费消息，这似乎非常
similar to the poor model and it in a
类似于可怜的模型，它在
way is because we are only pulling data
方式是因为我们只提取数据
and the publishers not allowed to signal
并且发布者不可以发信号
more data than we have asked him to send
比我们要求他发送的数据更多
us but here we are able to patch
我们，但在这里我们能够打补丁
together these requests so instead of
将这些请求放在一起，而不是
pulling three times i can just say
拉三下我只能说
request three elements and wait for the
请求三个元素并等待
publisher to do this and also because I
出版商这样做，也是因为我
know my buffer space I am able to just
知道我能够缓冲的空间
look at my buffer space and estimate how
看看我的缓冲区空间并估算
many elements I'm able to consume safely
我可以安全食用的许多元素
so here is that yeah my buffer is able
所以这是我的缓冲区能够
to come to still keep free elements so I
来仍然保留自由元素，所以我
told the publisher request free and he
告诉发布者免费请求，他
will eventually signal me free elements
最终会向我发出自由元素的信号
they all have this pre-allocated space
他们都有这个预先分配的空间
in the buffer so I'm not gonna blow up
在缓冲区中，所以我不会炸毁
my memory in the other situation where
我在其他情况下的记忆
we have it fast subscriber the protocol
我们有快速的订户协议
doesn't change right it's the same but
不会改变，是一样的，但是
I'm able to patch together v3 quest
我能够修补v3任务
signals and say request 6 or every time
发出信号并说出要求6或每次
I make my buffer empty say request time
我把缓冲区空了说请求时间
because with my buffer size so where is
因为我的缓冲区大小在哪里
it is more field for well intelligent
更适合聪明的领域
algorithms with find human the request
查找人的请求的算法
strategy because I know how the system
策略，因为我知道系统
is behaving I can adjust the number of
表现出我可以调整的数量
elements and requesting at frontline
要素和前线要求
based on however assistance performing
基于协助执行
and of course because this is a
当然，因为这是一个
synchronous we can send these requests
同步，我们可以发送这些请求
signals whenever we want right and we
只要我们想要正确就发出信号，我们
are still guaranteed to be safe okay one
仍然可以保证安全吗
other thing of course the publisher can
出版商当然可以做的其他事情
accumulate this demand so if I tell the
积累需求，所以如果我告诉
publisher request free he doesn't emit
发布者要求免费，但他不会发出
any data and then I say again request
任何数据，然后我再说一遍
free and again when he's going to have a
当他要有一个自由的时候
total demand of nine maybe he is also
九个人的总需求也许他也是
waiting for the data from some other
等待其他数据
point right environment when he gets the
当他得到正确的环境时
data he can start sending it and
数据，他可以开始发送它，
consuming his total accumulated demand
消耗了他的累计总需求
because we never signal more than we can
因为我们永远不会发出更多的信号
just be signaled we are still safe in
只是被告知我们仍然安全
this case on the subscribe event because
这种情况发生在订阅事件上，因为
we won't be signaling more requests then
我们不会再发出更多请求
we are ready to consume so once we have
我们准备消费，所以一旦
sent requests my entire buffers filesize
发送的请求我的整个缓冲区文件大小
we just wait until we get some signals
我们只是等到收到一些信号
up from upstream so we'll second biscuit
从上游开始，所以我们将第二块饼干
um very special case and in some cases
um非常特殊的情况，在某些情况下
you perhaps really now but for
你现在也许真的是
subscriber will be faster like way
订户会更快
faster than the publisher and the
比发布商和
reactive three specification we allow
我们允许的无功三种规格
for requesting long maxvill so this is a
请求长maxvill，所以这是一个
huge number and not really able to be
数量庞大，但实际上并不能成为
saturated and this makes will allow the
饱和，这将使
publisher to go with max speed and some
发布商以最大的速度和一些
kinds of systems that may be useful so
可能有用的各种系统
the spec doesn't forbid fits it's still
规范不禁止适合它仍然
fine what you had we're really opted out
很好，您真的选择了我们
of back pressure in this case right so
在这种情况下的背压是正确的
you have to understand what you're doing
你必须了解自己在做什么
once you request max value because
一旦您请求最大值，是因为
there's no way out after this one and
这之后没有出路了
let's look at the pipelining in reactive
让我们看一下反应式管道
strings so imagine you have three stages
字符串，所以想象你有三个阶段
because it's stream is composed of
因为它的流是由
different stages and each does its own
不同的阶段，每个阶段都有自己的特点
thing to a processing and processed
东西来处理
element
元件
and let's say on the left we have the
假设左侧有
sauce the publishers data on the right
填充右侧的发布者数据
we have first think the subscriber of
我们首先想到的是
some data and in the middle we have
一些数据，中间有
something that is both in very active
两者都非常活跃的东西
three specification we call this a
三个规范，我们称之为
processor so it is both a publisher and
处理器，因此它既是发布者又是
icicles and a subscriber so let's 11 um
冰柱和订阅者，让我们11微米
a typical use case I'm about to start
我即将开始的典型用例
processing the stream of data but I
处理数据流，但我
didn't yet generate demand because maybe
尚未产生需求，因为也许
if I had subscribers starting up it
如果我有订户启动它
needs to allocate some stuff but the
需要分配一些东西，但是
publishers may be ready well maybe it
发布者可能已经准备好了
can pre fetch some data to be able to
可以预取一些数据以能够
even more swiftly response to the first
对第一个反应甚至更快
requested gets so this is the eager
请求得到，所以这是渴望
eager publishing it started start up the
渴望发布它开始启动
loads of data and then it waits for
加载数据，然后等待
requests so it can again load up data
请求，以便它可以再次加载数据
into it buffer to be ready to signal as
进入缓冲区准备发信号
soon as it gets some demand so it's
只要有一些需求，那就是
growing some stuff in this buffer and
在这个缓冲区中生长一些东西，
when the downstream is finally ready to
当下游终于准备好
consume we can burn signal yeah Rico's 5
消耗掉我们可以燃烧的信号是的Rico 5
to the processor in the middle it it van
到中间的处理器
doesn't have to propagate the same
不必传播相同的
demand and it depends right it depends
需求，这取决于权利
on how the processor is implemented it
关于处理器的实现方式
depends on its logic but yeah it's
取决于它的逻辑，但是是的
propagated them on and then we are able
传播他们，然后我们能够
to signal the four or however elements
发出四个或所有元素的信号
we had preloaded in this case we signal
在这种情况下，我们已经预装了信号
four elements because this was the
四个要素，因为这是
number of elements free love with it in
元素数量释放对它的爱
the publisher so we have a demand of two
发布者，所以我们有两个需求
still available you got six signaled for
仍然可用，您收到了六个信号
Tuesday left we the publisher will now
星期二离开了，出版商现在会
keep fetching new data into his buffer
不断获取新数据到他的缓冲区
and one sits and sits ready it will
一个人坐着准备好了
again signal it downstream okay and
再次向下游发出信号，然后
since all this happens asynchronously
因为所有这些都是异步发生的
we're going to end up with this picture
我们将以这张照片结束
of everybody having some amount of
每个人都有一定数量的
demand
需求
and a synchronous signaling downstream
和下游的同步信令
but at the same time every element in
但同时，每个元素
the processing pipeline will be able to
处理管道将能够
reserve some buffer space and signal
保留一些缓冲空间和信号
demand upstream all the time so the
一直要求上游，所以
general idea is but the buffer space is
总体思路是，但缓冲区空间是
used in both ways it is kind of reserved
两种方式都使用它是保留的
because we are signaling demand and we
因为我们在传达需求，我们
keep space for it and we are expecting a
保留空间，我们期待
bunch of elements to comment so the
一堆要评论的元素
green and blue reserved spaces in the
绿色和蓝色保留空间
buffer for incoming elements elements
传入元素的缓冲区
which I'm expecting to be signaled soon
我希望很快能收到通知
and with all goes in or directv yeah to
并全力以赴或直接
the source of the data now the important
数据来源现在很重要
thing and no one has to wait in the
东西，没有人必须等待
system except if there is a flow element
系统，除非有流量元件
which doesn't signal demand upstream
这并不意味着上游需求
then we are waiting for that guy to
那我们在等那个家伙
finally signals in demand but if it is
最终发出需求信号，如果是
able to progress at a steady rate we
能够以稳定的速度前进
don't have to wait for anyone okay the
不必等待任何人都可以
SPI and it looks like this so we have a
SPI，看起来像这样，所以我们有一个
publisher until they subscribe method
发布者，直到他们订阅方法
the subscriber can subscribe to the
订户可以订阅
publisher site publisher gives them to
发布者网站发布者将其提供给
be subscribed by subscription and yeah
被订阅订阅，是的
there you have the subscriber so the
那里有订户，所以
general idea is that for subscription j
总体思路是，对于订阅j
is a shared secret and a way of
是一个共享的秘密和一种
communicating in between the publisher
在发布者之间进行沟通
on the subscribe so whenever I said your
在订阅上，所以每当我说您
signal demand here I mean that for
这里的信号需求是指
subscriber because it has for
订户，因为它具有
subscription can call the request method
订阅可以调用请求方法
which signal demands to the publisher so
向发布商发出信号的要求
how does a cough it alters as I said
如我所说，咳嗽如何改变
them well as I said in the beginning
正如我一开始所说的那样
this is not a very fancy API of course
当然，这不是一个非常好的API
you can implement anything you want with
您可以用任何东西来实现
it but it's just a bit hard I mean
它，但是有点困难，我是说
normally you would like to have
通常你想要
processing steps which are like filter
处理步骤类似于过滤器
or math or
或数学或
or concat that kind of operations here
或在这里进行这种操作
we don't really have that we have the
我们真的没有，我们有
low level building blocks which enabled
低级别的构建基块
the backpressure nursing from this
背压护理由此
behavior so acha fits into the picture
行为，所以恰如其分
of providing these high-level
提供这些高级
abstractions so for those who haven't
对于那些没有抽象的人
seen or heard about occur before acha
看过或听说过发生在阿差之前
has a bunch of modules we tend to think
有很多我们倾向于认为的模块
of it as a toolkit move in the framework
作为工具箱在框架中移动
and yeah it's aimed for high-performance
是的，它的目标是高性能
concurrency and also clustering and
并发以及集群和
distributed systems so that's our goal
分布式系统，这就是我们的目标
and what the main modules is a collector
主要模块是什么
and actor are actors are a abstraction
演员是演员，是抽象
which provide you a very limited in a
这为您提供了非常有限的
way set of features so it an actor can
功能集，演员可以
only send or receive messages create
仅发送或接收消息创建
other actors or change its behavior so
其他参与者或改变其行为
this is in a way limited but in another
这在某种程度上是受限制的，但在另一方面
way and you can model anything you want
方式，您可以建模任何您想要的
in it nawl so it's a great abstraction
在它的钉子里，这是一个很棒的抽象
for concurrent systems you are basically
对于并发系统，您基本上
freed from many kinds of races and
从许多种族中解脱出来
inside an actor you don't have to worry
在演员里面，你不必担心
about concurrent access to mutable data
关于并发访问可变数据
structures say so that's the core of
结构说，这就是
what we have this is how an actor looks
我们所拥有的就是演员的模样
so you implement an actor by extending
因此您可以通过扩展来实现演员
actor you have a received method the
演员你有收到方法
next turn is a redness at you would be
下一回合你会发红
given by someone and then you can reply
由某人给予，然后您可以回复
to the sender of this message using the
发送给该邮件的发件人
tariff reader so you would treat for us
收费阅读器，让您为我们服务
sender tell decide move well decide move
发件人告诉决定移动好决定移动
is something that decides you next move
是决定你下一步行动的东西
in some game for example so this is the
例如在某些游戏中，这是
core versus a bunch of other modules
核心与其他模块
like clustering and persistence for
例如集群和持久性
securus even sourcing but let's talk
securus甚至进行采购，但让我们谈谈
about extremes that's what the talk is
关于极端的话题
about right so and the design goals are
大约是正确的，设计目标是
to be superior in reusable performant
在可重用性能方面表现出色
and yeah and specifically we really care
是的，特别是我们真的很在乎
about these bound buffer spaces maybe
关于这些绑定的缓冲区空间
you have heard me
你听过我
oh you have seconds ago ranting about
哦，你有几秒钟前在抱怨
Buffy space this is because we really
布菲空间这是因为我们真的
care about this okay now the question is
关心这个好吧，现在的问题是
why do we care about buffer space so
为什么我们要关心缓冲区空间
imagine you have faced mmhmm yeah number
想象你遇到了mmhmm是的
web server it maybe even a chat cell and
网络服务器，甚至是聊天室，
then imagine you know that you are able
然后想象你知道你有能力
to process this request using a stream
使用流处理此请求
pipeline because this is actually how we
管道，因为这实际上是我们
expose in our HTTP and upcoming module
在我们的HTTP和即将发布的模块中公开
how you process TCP connections and HTTP
您如何处理TCP连接和HTTP
connections right so imagine you are
连接正确，所以想象你是
able to model and exactly reason about
能够建模并确切说明
the buffer space which will be used by
缓冲区空间将由
every stream in your system so in this
您系统中的每个流
case I have a one connection and it's
如果我有一个连接，那是
never using more date more space fun
从来没有使用更多的日期更多的空间乐趣
than shown in the graph normally maybe
比正常情况下的图表所示
it would be more wonky maybe it would
也许会更古怪
jump up and down and cause a lot of GC
上下跳跃并导致大量GC
in our case we have this pre-allocated
在我们的情况下，我们已经预先分配了
buffer spaces and we just reuse them so
缓冲空间，我们只是重复使用它们
was going to be a more stable memory
本来会更稳定的记忆
wise performance and you can estimate
明智的表现，你可以估计
how many connections am i able to
我能连接多少个
consume on this server if it has got 800
在此服务器上消耗（如果它有800）
megs of ram ok but no tuve API so the
好的ram，但没有tuve API，所以
API uses slightly different wording van
API使用略有不同的措辞范
Vere active streams one and this is also
Vere活动流一个，这也是
by by choice and because we are modeling
通过选择，因为我们正在建模
a bit higher higher level abstractions
更高层次的抽象
so we need better words for it so if lo
所以我们需要更好的语言，如果
is something that has exactly one input
是只有一个输入的东西
and exactly one output so think of it as
恰好有一个输出，所以可以认为是
map map is a great example right if you
地图map是一个很好的例子，如果您
have a collection you can map over it
有一个收藏可以映射
and from a collection of ends you can
从目的出发，您可以
may today make it into a collection of
今天可以将其纳入
strength for exam this would be a flaw
考试的力量，这将是一个缺陷
sir madam have sources sources are where
夫人女士，有资源，来源在哪里
the data comes from and they have
数据来自，他们有
exactly one not bound and the output
恰好一个不绑定和输出
port and they sink which has exactly one
港口，他们沉没，其中有一个
not bound port which is its impt
没有绑定的端口，这是它的目的
and yeah transformation wise you can
是的，转型明智，您可以
just put a transformation into a map
只是将变换放入地图
step witchy witch in code looks like
代码中的一步巫婆巫婆看起来像
this so have a float double and we make
所以有一个浮点双，我们做
it to an it another way of thinking
这是另一种思考方式
about these is just thinking about yeah
关于这些只是在想
it's a pipe and you can pipe things
这是一个管道，你可以管道的东西
fruit and also um yeah worth noting I
水果，嗯，也值得一提
said it that it is not yet as attached
说它还没有附上
to a source right so when we sell it
来源权，所以当我们出售它时
flowed over you're only saying this
流过你只是在说这个
stream is ready to work on double
流已准备好进行双打
doesn't yet have a source attached okay
还没有附加源
some aqua basics for for those who are
对于那些谁是一些水的基础知识
not familiar with it anaka we have
我们不熟悉anaka
something called an active system and
称为主动系统的东西
actor system is something that contains
演员系统是包含
all the actors in your application and
您应用程序中的所有参与者
it's basically a set of fred pools and
它基本上是一组水池
configuration and a registry for
配置和注册表
locating and doing things with actors
与演员定位并做事
and and then we need a flow materialized
然后我们需要实现的流程
so we flow materializer is for a guy who
所以我们流物质化是为一个谁
is responsible of taking a flow
负责流
description and graph description of his
他的描述和图形描述
processing pipeline and turning it into
处理管道并将其变成
a running my thing that is actually on
运行我实际上正在运行的东西
doing stuff with his data so determines
用他的数据做事，因此确定
what path the interesting thing is
有趣的是什么路
because we have you lifted
因为我们让你举起
representation of this flow processing
此流程处理的表示
graph when which means that anyone could
当什么时候表示，任何人都可以
write a flow materializer not here
在此处写一个流物化器
realize it into a different processing
将其实现为不同的处理
pipeline but the description is really
管道，但描述确实
the same right you can run a map
同样的权利，您可以运行地图
computational spark you can run in that
您可以在其中运行计算火花
computation on acha but you could also
在acha上进行计算，但您也可以
run it on Hadoop if you really want
如果您真的想在Hadoop上运行它
right so this is an interesting feature
对，所以这是一个有趣的功能
not yet utilized but we hope it will so
尚未利用，但我们希望如此
um our flow materializes currently actor
嗯，我们的工作流实现了当前的演员
based server operations will be backed
基于服务器的操作将得到支持
by actors and they communicate a
由演员和他们交流
synchronous via using messaging
通过使用消息传递进行同步
and of course you can configure it then
当然您可以配置它
and now is the first time we see a sink
现在是我们第一次看到水槽
in action so here we have a sink for
在行动中，所以在这里我们有一个沉
each that for each end we'll do
每个目的，我们都会做
something with it and when you place a
东西，当你放置一个
function that we get this each element
我们得到每个元素的功能
right and then the simplest way to the
对，然后是最简单的方法
hello world of our co streams is a
您的合作流的世界是
source one two three which will produce
源一二三将产生
in these elements one two and three and
在这些元素一二和三
then you run it to the sink which will
然后将其运行到水槽
effectively just print it I'll talk a
有效地只是打印它，我会说
little bit further down the line about
再往下走一点
why it is so that we have separate
为什么这样，我们有分开
things for it now some libraries have
现在的事情有些图书馆
chosen to have just one abstraction we
选择只有一种抽象
have chosen to have these different ones
选择了这些不同的
and think that it's easier to model and
并认为建模和建模更容易
reason about these things if I know if
如果我知道这些事情的原因
its source or sink and how does it
它的来源或下沉以及如何
actually materialize it uses ventas it
实际上实现它使用ventas
flow materializer for non scarlett
非斯嘉丽流化剂
people and actual explanation so
人和实际的解释，所以
implicit means when you see the implicit
隐式意味着当您看到隐式
viral NAT from a tube that Liza it means
从Liza意味着管中的病毒NAT
that we can skip writing the parentheses
我们可以跳过写括号
Matt in the line where we have run with
马特（Matt）
for each sink this means less passing
对于每个水槽，这意味着更少的通过
around parameters and we always have
围绕参数，我们总是有
some fuel materializing scope so the
一些燃料实现范围，因此
compiler does his work for us the Java
编译器为我们做他的工作Java
API is because it's also fully usable
API是因为它也完全可用
from Java actually very similar to this
来自Java实际上与此非常相似
specific especially with Java 8 where we
特别是在Java 8中
now have done that it looks very similar
现在已经完成，看起来非常相似
in most cases yeah except the
在大多数情况下，除了
materializer has to be for example
物化器必须是例如
pressed explicitly and that kind of
明确地按
small cosmetic changes so if you are a
小小的化妆品变化，所以如果你是一个
Java guy you can use it from the whole
Java家伙，您可以从整体上使用它
so yeah the typical question is why ever
是的，典型的问题是为什么
run with so the run with is we run with
与运行，所以与我们一起运行
some kind of thing but for some kinds of
某种东西，但是对于某种
operations like for reach and forward we
像前进和前进一样的行动
have pre-built what are sugars on source
已经预建了什么是糖
so you can call it explicitly source for
因此您可以将其明确地称为
each print line
每条印刷线
this is a terminal operation mind you
这是终端操作的想法
the terminal operations I mean something
终端操作我的意思是
that actually materializes with you says
实际上与您实现
we'll start running at this point when
我们将在此时开始运行
you write for for each and same with all
你为每一个都写
the methods with have run in their names
带有名称的方法
we are currently in the process of
我们目前正在
renaming these so for each will be
重命名这些，以便每个
called run for each and Ford will be run
称为每个运行，福特将运行
called run Ford so whenever you see a
叫运行福特，所以每当你看到一个
method with run in the beginning that
开头的方法
will not realize refer so a bunch of
不会意识到引用，所以一堆
type safety things we have in NACO
输入我们在NACO中拥有的安全物品
streams so I said but the flow is not
流，所以我说，但流不是
yet attached to a source but and I did
仍附加到来源，但我做到了
it is also not attached to a sink so you
它也没有连接到水槽，所以你
cannot just attach it to a swap to a
不能只是将它附加到交换
sink and expect it to run that won't
下沉并期望它运行不会
compile because it needs both so yep
编译是因为它既需要
here so in this example I'm showing I
在这里，在这个例子中，我向我展示
have a flow that is um not connected to
流量未连接到um
anything yet I cannot run with it but if
一切我都无法运行，但是如果
you take the flow and then connected to
你采取流程，然后连接到
its source ah oh sorry I i have a
它的来源啊，对不起，我有一个
mistake in this basically what this says
这基本上是什么意思
is you have to attach to both sides you
是你必须两面都依附吗
can have materialized something in a
可以在
vacuum oh that's a that's a better
真空哦，那是一个更好的
example so when you have a flow you can
例如，当您有流程时，您可以
map these into a string and then you can
将它们映射成字符串，然后就可以
give it both ends of processing program
给它处理程序的两端
so the sauce 1 to 10 in the sink which
所以水槽中的酱料1到10
is just in black hosting it will ignore
只是在黑色主机它将忽略
the data that is coming to it and
即将到来的数据
interesting thing to say is the flows
有趣的事情是流量
are reusable which means that you can
可重复使用，这意味着您可以
construct this pipeline once and values
一次构造这个管道并值
it with multiple sources this is also
它有多个来源，这也是
interesting because you can construct
有趣，因为您可以构建
this complex processing pipeline just
这个复杂的处理管道
once keep it cached another in the value
一旦保持它缓存另一个值
and then just use it multiple times to
然后多次使用
run for each week was fed is coming into
每周运行一次，喂饱了
your system for example
例如您的系统
here we have a slightly more complex
这里我们稍微复杂一点
case and also here is a slide sneak peek
案例，这也是偷看幻灯片
of how you integrate with my co-actors
如何与我的合作者融合
so you just have the actor subscriber
所以你只有演员订阅者
which will then get all these elements
然后将获得所有这些元素
which is signaled by further upstream
上游发出信号
processing pipeline and you have all the
处理管道，您拥有了所有
usual things like mad filter drop group
疯狂过滤器掉落组之类的平常事物
by and group by a specifically
通过和按特定分组
interesting because it produces a stream
有趣，因为它产生了一个流
of streams let's look at how this looks
的流让我们看一下它的外观
so because I am getting some kind of
所以因为我得到某种
numbers and 13 12 11 and when I group by
数字和13 12 11以及当我分组时
the last and siphon number I'm gonna get
我会得到的最后一个虹吸号码
groups that are um could be
嗯，可能是
characterized as the thing that ends
表征为终结的事物
with a one and you get van out of this
与一个人，你会得到范
group by operator a stream that signals
按操作员分组信号流
a pair of group key to my case it would
一对我的案子的钥匙
be one than 20 and 3 and for each of
是20和3之一，并且每个
those gives you a sub stream of this so
这些给你这个的子流
when you can consume the sub stream or
当您可以使用子流或
cancel it if you're not interested in
如果您不感兴趣，请取消
two in things ending with the number two
以第二个结尾的第二个
you can just cancel the sub stream and
您可以取消子流，然后
just consume those you want to come in
只吃那些你想进来的
this is very interesting because then
这很有趣，因为
normally you would expect collections
通常你会期望收集
here right but in streams land you
在这里，但是在溪流中
really have to stop thinking about
真的必须停止思考
collections and just streams because a
集合和只是流，因为
stream can be potentially infinite right
流可能是无限的权利
you cannot easily in fit infinite
你不能轻易适应无限
elements into memory at least not on
元素至少不能进入内存
current computers right so this is where
当前的计算机正确，所以这是
everything is a stream and you can apply
一切都是流，您可以申请
stream operations to each other for sub
彼此进行流操作以进行子操作
streams and the group by again or do
流和再次分组或做
different things okay yeah when you can
是的，不同的事情好吗
consume the sub streams and different
消耗子流和不同
different things which flows but the
流动的不同事物，但
thing I want to talk about today is
我今天要谈的是
graph processing so this is a rather
图形处理，所以这是一个相当
unique thing to our costumes most of
我们服装的独特之处
other libraries are not so focused on
其他图书馆不是那么专注
complex draft processing as we are think
我们认为复杂的草稿处理
so ananka streams faces covered a flow
所以阿南卡溪流的面孔覆盖了流
graph so whenever you see these f1 f2 f3
图，所以每当您看到这些f1 f2 f3
f4 imagine that is a flow but it's just
f4想象这是一个流程，但这仅仅是
a linear string right and but what about
线性字符串对，但是那又怎么样
these broadcast and merge things these
这些广播和合并这些东西
are what we call fan and fan out
这就是我们所说的“扇出”
operations are also just junctions so um
操作也只是交界处
let's look at this example the simplest
让我们看看这个例子中最简单的
were not simplest but very simple graph
不是最简单但非常简单的图形
and try to model it and then we look
然后尝试建模，然后我们看一下
into how the extremes dsl for graphs
进入图表的极限DSL
actually works so also the design goal
实际上有效，因此设计目标
of this dsl is too when you have your
当您拥有自己的dsl时
design session you draw some stuff on
在设计会议上您要画些东西
the whiteboard and basically it will end
白板，基本上它将结束
up more or less like this and it's going
这样或多或少地上升
to be circles it's going to be arrows so
变成圆圈，它将变成箭头，所以
the design goal here is to make the
这里的设计目标是使
circulus graph element and make four
圆周图元素，使四个
lines normal flow elements so let me
线条正常的流动元素，所以让我
have yard with some coloring in this
在这有一些颜色的院子
case every F so every linear Porton
每个F的情况，每个线性Porton
processing is mapped to a flow and value
处理映射到流程和价值
to different stuff which types for
不同类型的东西
example f1 will take the input and went
示例f1将接受输入并转到
up it to an intermediate value then f2
上调到中间值然后f2
and the four will make these
而四个将使这些
intermediate values into some enriched
中间值变成一些丰富的
values and then we can just filter them
值，然后我们可以过滤它们
in F free and yeah and this are the
在F free中，这是
linear operation for the news now let's
现在新闻的线性运算
look at the graph equations so we start
看图方程，所以我们开始
this by making a flow graph and when we
通过制作流程图，当我们
import the flow graph implicit to make
导入隐式生成的流程图
face quickly arrow operator available
快速面对箭头运算符可用
and then we simply connect these so when
然后我们简单地连接这些，这样当
you notice for because which is
您会注意到，因为这是
broadcast and worse things we just first
广播和更糟糕的事情，我们只是第一
define them so you have a very cost
定义它们，所以您要付出很高的代价
which is a broadcast of intermediate
这是一个中间的广播
values broadcast means every subscriber
价值观广播意味着每个订户
would get the same value wouldn't came
将获得相同的价值不会
into this broadcast and then we have
进入这个广播，然后我们有
emerged we
出现了我们
we'll just take from one or the other
我们只是从一个或另一个
incoming stream and produces out coming
流入并产生流出
most stream so we declare those and then
大多数流，所以我们声明这些，然后
we use them so when you look at the
我们使用它们，所以当您查看
graph on the top does f1 come in either
顶部的图是否会出现f1
broadcast and from a broadcast we have
广播和广播
to and a four and then the dr said you
到和四，然后博士说你
can see it's pretty similar to what the
可以看到它与
graph looks like on the whiteboard so
图看起来像白板上的
that was a explicit in design goal and i
那是一个明确的设计目标，我
think it's i think it's much i'm curious
以为是我很好奇
to hear your opinions about it feel free
随时听听您的意见
to Sharon so I said first previously
沙龙，所以我之前先说
about froze but let me reiterate that
关于冻结，但让我重申
once you have a flow graph it is
一旦有了流程图，它就是
immutable and safe to share between
一成不变，可以安全地共享
threads and actually we're going to we
线程，实际上我们要去
are aiming to make it a possible to
旨在使其成为可能
share between nodes in justice because
在正义的节点之间共享，因为
it is just a description of how we run
这只是我们运作方式的描述
to run things so in theory it could be
运行事物，因此从理论上讲
freely shared across clusters but we're
在集群之间自由共享，但我们
not varied that's a future plan so we
没有变化，这是一个未来的计划，所以我们
have 20 minutes so right on time so I'm
有20分钟的时间准时所以我
gonna jump into some examples let's so
要跳入一些例子，让我们这样
let me open up IntelliJ here not this
让我在这里打开IntelliJ
one not this one yes this one so um have
一个不是这个一个是这个这个嗯
a few examples prepared and let's see
准备了一些示例，让我们看看
how how much time we have left no after
我们有多少时间没有离开过
a few and then we decided for going to
一些，然后我们决定去
get and jump into Q&amp;A right way oh if
正确地进入并跳入问答环节，哦，如果
we're gonna do an example more so the
我们将再做一个例子，这样
reader and to reiterate how useless
读者并重申如何无用
thing you have an active system a floor
你有一个活跃的系统地板
materializer I import a system
实现我导入系统
dispersion just to have something to
分散只是为了要
execute futures on well that's not
在不是很好的情况下执行期货
really a car specific thing that is a
真的是汽车特有的东西
one scholar future specific thing so
一位学者未来的具体事情如此
however you want to do this let's have a
但是，您想这样做，让我们
source and let's see what kinds of
来源，让我们看看是哪种
sources we can have so sources can be
我们可以拥有的资源，因此可以是
from actors fits for props a source can
来自演员的适合道具的来源可以
be made from a graph actually
实际上是由图制成的
it can be a timer sauce which is very
它可以是一个计时器酱，这是非常
nice read delay into a ver and tick okay
很好的读取延迟到ver并打勾好
then we can have a source from the
那么我们可以从
future and it's rubber or a factory of
未来，它是橡胶或
iterated or we can simply consume a
迭代，否则我们可以简单地消耗一个
reactive streams publisher in our case
在我们的案例中反应流发布者
let's do something fine let's say hello
让我们做点好事，我们打个招呼
and see her word and and two listed so
看到她的话和另外两个这样
now it's going to be a list of
现在将是
characters what can we do with this so
角色我们该怎么办
there's a number of different things so
有很多不同的事情，所以
for example we can drop a bunch of
例如，我们可以放一堆
elements filter group by new Soviet one
元素过滤器组由新苏维埃一
ready but we're going to do the usual
准备好了，但我们要照常做
traditional thing sub car so the
传统的东西子车所以
incoming thing is a car yeah all right
进来的东西是一辆车，是的，好的
and then we can say C to upper wall
然后我们可以对上壁说C
Scarlett syntax why we can do this means
Scarlett语法为何可以做到这一点
the same thing and yeah so what if I
是的，是的，如果我
want to add some exclamation marks at
想要在添加一些感叹号
the end of this we have an operator for
最后，我们有一个运算符
that it's called concat in concord means
它在一致中被称为concat意味着
take this first source and drain it and
拿走第一个来源并将其排干
then once you're done draining the first
然后，一旦您耗尽了第一个
source start draining the second one so
源开始排第二个
in our case we can start draining same
在我们的情况下，我们可以开始排水
thing not for most amazing like example
事情不是最令人惊讶的，例如例子
here but it's interesting because you
在这里，但是很有趣，因为你
can combine different sources of data
可以合并不同的数据源
and then the concord would basically
然后这个和解基本上
serve yet the first source of data is
提供数据的第一个来源是
depleted continue with the second source
耗尽继续第二个来源
of the data which is exactly what's
数据到底是什么
happening here and then we can maybe
发生在这里，然后我们也许
first start with the usual more of a
首先从通常的
both way so we have a sink object Anaka
两种方式，所以我们有一个下沉对象Anaka
and this sink has a bunch of helper left
这个水槽还剩下一帮手
so here you can see all the kinds of
所以在这里您可以看到各种各样的
think we provide and so for example sink
认为我们提供了，例如下沉
head means the first element that goes
头是指第一个元素
through the entire stream in our case it
在整个案例中
would be an age so not very interesting
将是一个年龄，所以不是很有趣
so let's use IE for each actually for it
所以让我们为每个实际使用IE
would be interesting so 40 mins take
会很有趣，所以需要40分钟
some valium and while the stream is
一些安定的，而流是
giving you new values accumulate them
给您新的价值积累
into a new move n oq Ford zero
迈入新步伐福特零
accumulator and car nice so that's the
蓄能器和汽车很好，所以
car as the accumulator and we can say X
汽车作为蓄能器，我们可以说X
plus C so what does cos actually eat it
加C那么cos到底吃了什么
so because this is a run with and put
所以因为这是一次
materialize the flow and run it here the
实现流程并在此处运行
implicit from materializes use from 913
从913隐含实现
right and the value will actually be a
对，值实际上将是
future future of string future of string
字符串的未来字符串的未来
I say scar upon current future right
我对当前的未来感到恐惧
because because we don't really know
因为因为我们真的不知道
when the stream is going to finish if it
当流将要结束时
will finish ever right and then we can
将永远正确完成，然后我们可以
on the value perform a map on maybe are
在值上执行地图可能是
complete and complete tags and text
完整的标签和文本
and we can just move the shutdown code I
我们可以移动关闭代码
have under here into this guy let me
在这家伙之下
fire up conclusion now I have a compile
得出结论，现在我有一个编译
error in a different yep now let's try
错误，现在尝试
to run this guy what now so the
经营这个家伙，现在怎么办
configuration wasn't to help in IntelliJ
配置并不能帮助IntelliJ
and I consulates fine so let's jump to
我领事很好，让我们跳到
the console whoop here we have a console
控制台在这里，我们有一个控制台
you can see I fired up running a word
你可以看到我开火了
and wrote successful word this is
并写了成功的话，这是
because one complete reps of the night
因为一个夜晚的完整代表
right so it can be a success or failure
对，所以它可以是成功或失败
okay let's talk about graphs here I have
好吧，让我们在这里谈谈图表
a simple graph which is basically the
一个简单的图，基本上是
exact same thing that we had before on
与我们以前完全一样的事情
the slides so timewise actually let's
如此及时的幻灯片实际上让我们
jump to the or just simply show how you
跳到或只是显示您如何
can easily write this one so we
可以轻松地写这个，所以我们
calculate a bar min cost which is a
计算一个棒的最小成本是
broadcast of intermediate values and
广播中间值和
then I need emerge okay let's use the
那么我需要出现好吧，让我们使用
different elements to make it a bit more
不同的元素使它变得更多
interesting so this is going to be the
有趣，所以这将是
zip so as it is something that takes
拉链，因为它需要一些东西
exactly two two streams and zips to them
恰好两个两个流并压缩到它们
together in a pair
在一起在一起
of things and also notice that we have a
的事情，还请注意，我们有一个
scar a dsl and the java d so this is
疤痕的DSL和Java的D，所以这是
because of course and we try to make the
因为当然，我们尝试使
best dsl possible for every language so
每种语言最好的DSL
what looks nice in scarlet doesn't
猩红色看起来不错的东西
necessarily look nice and avant in the
一定看起来不错，在
inverse weight also so when I zip from
重量也相反，所以当我从
the scholar dear sir I will be getting a
学者先生，先生，我会得到一个
scarlet opera we have something that is
猩红色歌剧，我们有一些东西是
called the top really test two elements
叫顶真的考了两个要素
and when we zip in Java dear sir we get
当我们用Java压缩亲爱的先生时，我们得到
a Java pair we have a helper class for
一个Java对，我们有一个辅助类
that so it's more usable for for our
这样对我们来说更有用
users which tend to just use job they
倾向于只使用工作的用户
are first-class citizen in a way so I'm
是一流的公民，所以我
going to zip to enriched things right
压缩丰富的东西吧
let's prepared and now from the input
让我们准备，现在从输入
through f1 through the broadcast and the
通过f1通过广播和
values the small format phone and
重视小尺寸手机，
through f2 pflugers left so notice and
通过f2冒起者离开，所以请注意并
whereas broadcast to just feed into it
而广播只是馈送给它
gzip actually has designated names for
gzip实际上已经为
its inputs so here we want to found a
它的输入，所以在这里我们想找到一个
broadcast through a for I believe in to
通过我相信的广播
not wear left input but number right
不穿左输入但右穿
this is also type 60 the first type here
这也是60型
is for left finger the second type here
是左手的第二种类型
is the right input and when I'm gonna
是正确的输入，当我要
Murphy's Raj
墨菲的拉杰
oh sorry once it shows sorry sorry sorry
哦，对不起，一旦显示抱歉，对不起
i meant to say zip the fount so we have
我的意思是说要压缩拉链，所以我们有
the output of this visit element and i
此visit元素的输出和
have to sink it into some something so
必须沉入一些东西，所以
here I had a publisher thing which
在这里我有一个出版商的东西
exposes a reactive streams publisher for
公开一个反应式流发布者
consumption for anyone was to continue
任何人的消费都将继续
it but yeah it was just a enriched
但是，是的，这只是一个丰富的
whereas now I have a pair of enriched
而现在我有一双
errands ok that's already one element
好吧，那已经是一个要素
more to know about and also um while we
还有更多的事情要知道，而同时我们
are here let's talk about netting
在这里让我们谈谈净额结算
because many of the other welcome n tape
因为许多其他欢迎磁带
us who you're working with exposed
我们与您一起工作的人暴露
futures right so they expose a future
期货对，所以他们暴露了未来
the result not just for value so here in
结果不只是为了价值，所以在这里
the intermediate trade we have a enrich
我们有丰富的中间贸易
or enrich ASIC this is aims to young act
或丰富ASIC，这是为了年轻的行为
like a navy HTTP call or something that
例如海军HTTP通话或其他
has to go out to something and
必须出去做点什么
eventually gives you back the result so
最终会给您结果
here I'm using in a for a nap async
在这里我正在使用一个小睡异步
operator which works exactly like map
完全类似于地图的运算符
but is able to extract the value from
但能够从中提取价值
the future and pass it along so we pass
未来并通过它，所以我们过去
on the element once the future to
在元素上一旦未来
succeed and successfully compete if it
成功并成功竞争
fails we pass along the failure and for
失败，我们通过失败，并为
the stream and yes this is all that in
流，是的，这就是全部
case you're wondering there's also an
如果您想知道还有一个
unordered case because if you're doing
无序的情况，因为如果你在做
multiple calls everybody is waiting a
每个人都在打多个电话
little bit before they complete with
在他们完成之前
future maybe you don't care about all
未来也许你不在乎所有
that you just want to proceed as fast as
您只想以最快的速度进行
you can so you want to generate the
您可以，因此您想生成
mountain demand as fast as you can the
尽可能快地满足山区需求
way to generate demand is to clear out
产生需求的方法是清除
processing just keep processing stuff so
处理只是保持处理的东西，所以
you want to process not in the water but
您要处理的不是水中的，而是
unordered as fast as you can so but
尽可能快地无序，但是
small little trivia that may be helpful
小小的琐事可能会有所帮助
in your processing pipelines
在您的处理管道中
so the next one I want to show you is
所以我要告诉你的下一个是
actually exactly um well not agree a
实际上，嗯，我不同意
improvement over what we saw now and
改善我们现在所看到的
this is gonna be well it's that's okay i
这会很好，没关系，我
have this left right this is kind of
有这个左边右边这是一种
meaningful especially for toppers but
有意义，特别是对于排行榜，但
when I have a person I want to map into
当我有一个人要映射到
a zip into a person how do I do that so
拉一个人，我该怎么做
there's a bunch of ways to do it but
有很多方法可以做到
first let's look at a simple case so I
首先让我们看一个简单的案例
can prepare my zip to be prepare my
可以准备我的拉链来准备我的拉链
class here it's going to be a simple one
在这里上课，这将是一个简单的
and my zip can now be a zip with and zip
现在我的zip可以是和的zip
wife is something that takes a function
妻子是有功能的
that we performed a zipping no nukes are
我们没有拉链的拉链
yes okay and then we can take in a name
是的，好的，然后我们可以输入一个名字
string and an edge which will be mapping
字符串和将要映射的边
to this person right doesn't itch so
对这个人来说不痒
this is a very robust way to put it
这是一种非常强大的表达方式
because now we can use the left and
因为现在我们可以使用左和
right to to zip into a person so the
压缩人的权利，因此
output of zip you relearn miss a bit
您重新学习的zip输出错过了一点
what was observed is now a person so
现在观察到的是一个人，所以
this is better but I was getting at how
这更好，但我正在了解如何
how can we make this even nicer so for
我们怎样才能使它变得更好
first things let's use some scholar
首先，让我们使用一些学者
goodness so we can collapse this entire
善良，所以我们可以使整个崩溃
nothing thing and to apply underscore
没事，要加下划线
which will infer the proper type so now
现在可以推断出正确的类型
zip you can see it will take a string
zip，您会看到它需要一个字符串
take an end in the middle person so this
结束中间人，所以这
is nice it's still not the best thing we
很好，但这仍然不是我们最好的东西
can do
可以做
so now I'm going to show the last
所以现在我要显示最后一个
example for today it would be a flex
今天的例子将是弹性
image which will allow us to write name
可以让我们写名字的图片
and H so we'll be able to have a nice
和H，这样我们就可以拥有一个不错的
processing growth that actually tells us
处理增长实际上告诉我们
what we are doing so here we'll have to
我们正在做的事情在这里，我们将不得不
say new probably call it a safe person
说新的可能称其为安全人
doesn't match start extends payflex
与开始不符会延长payflex
image it's going to emit a cursor and
图像将发出一个光标，
then we have to create this mouse logic
然后我们必须创建此鼠标逻辑
enough logic will be responsible for
足够的逻辑将负责
reading this data because it will decide
读取此数据，因为它将决定
from which element from rich incoming
来自丰富输入的元素
stream we do what and first we need to
流我们做什么，首先我们需要
define a name and create input port and
定义名称并创建输入端口，并
a name is a string and then we need H
一个名字是一个字符串，然后我们需要H
and H is in it so now you can see the
H在其中，所以现在您可以看到
lines 36 37 compile but it doesn't
第36 37行会编译，但不会
really get do what we wanted so we want
真正做到我们想要的，所以我们想要
to have a numerous logic remote logic of
具有众多逻辑远程逻辑
person and we can skip this type of
人，我们可以跳过这种类型的
notation and I will implement it rather
符号，我宁愿实现它
swiftly so we're not completely out of
迅速，所以我们并没有完全摆脱
time so first we have to give it all the
时间，所以首先我们必须全力以赴
handles between on I'm going to be using
处理之间，我将要使用
in this match so now our case is going
在这场比赛中，所以现在我们的情况是
to be named an age and then we'll use
被命名为年龄，然后我们将使用
and I should state and this is gonna be
我应该说，这将是
a state of wheat or inputs you can read
小麦状态或您可以阅读的输入
about vision and deeply hit the dogs but
关于视觉，并深深地打了狗，但
it does actually means i will emit an
它确实意味着我将发出一个
element whenever all inputs i want to be
每当我想成为所有输入的元素
reading sorry at all
读对不起
read or name and age so this means
阅读或姓名和年龄，这意味着
whenever verse an element on both of
每当两个元素上的元素
these read or and own name and on age I
这些读过的或自己的名字，以及我的年龄
want to trigger this function which is
想触发这个功能
context this is not interesting in our
在我们的上下文中这并不有趣
case this would normally contain which
这种情况通常包含
input was triggered but in our case we
输入被触发，但在我们的情况下，
trigger on all levels so we don't care
触发所有级别，所以我们不在乎
and then we can contact amit a person
然后我们可以联系给一个人
from n plus 9 and puts h and you have to
从n加9到h，你必须
return a same state because this state
返回相同状态，因为此状态
helper is actually a state machine so
助手实际上是一个状态机
whenever you get to emit an element you
每当你发出一个元素时
can become another state for example i
可以成为另一个状态，例如我
am now done and i will be completing
现在完成了，我将完成
this stream in our case we stay in the
在我们的情况下，这条流我们留在
same studied so this is how easily you
同样研究，所以这是你多么容易
can define your own mergers and there's
可以定义自己的合并，
also a helper for fan-out elements so
也是扇出元素的助手
that one is called a flexi route now
现在被称为弹性路线
let's jump back to slides and wrap up
让我们跳回幻灯片并结束
with questions so to wrap up what we did
有问题，以便总结我们所做的事情
and we talked a little bit about non non
我们谈到了非非
blocking back pressure how we do complex
阻止背压我们如何做复杂
rough processing pipelines and a bunch
粗加工管道和一堆
of custom elements now what we didn't
自定义元素现在我们没有
explore but was really a load of
探索，但实际上是
interesting stuff to see here is how to
有趣的东西在这里看到是如何
put an explicit buffering how to
放置一个显式缓冲如何
integrate our correctors if you have
如果有的话，整合我们的校正器
existing systems or just need full
现有系统或只需要完整的
control over what actors give you and
控制演员给你的东西，以及
time-based operations so take while two
基于时间的操作，因此需要两个
seconds that's kind of operations and
秒的操作和
what else do we have future plans so the
我们还有什么未来的计划，所以
current state of our streams is that we
我们流的当前状态是
are stabilizing the API and we are
正在稳定API，我们
aiming to release
旨在释放
you wanted already yeah maybe early next
你已经想要了，可能是下一个早
next month not next month and of course
下个月，当然不是下个月
we are working on documentation which is
我们正在处理文档
now getting a java version then we are
现在得到一个Java版本，那么我们是
improving the testability we want to
改善我们想要的可测试性
provide a test kit similar to how you
提供与您类似的测试套件
have test probes for a car normal a car
有针对汽车的测试探针
actors and the most important thing to
演员和最重要的事情
remember acha streams have not yet been
记住acha流还没有
performance student so you can expect a
表演学生，所以你可以期待
lot better performance because we have a
性能更好，因为我们有一个
bunch of and now on the bottlenecks and
一堆，现在在瓶颈上，
known to be solved bottlenecks we just
已知可以解决的瓶颈
have to solve them and we know how so
必须解决它们，我们知道如何解决
it's gonna be way faster and when you
它将变得更快，当您
play around around with it you may
随便玩吧
actually think that it's already fast
其实以为已经快了
enough as some some recent blog posts
足够一些最近的博客文章
the show on the interwebs it was quite
在互联网上的表演很
interesting so other than that it would
有趣的是，除此之外
be great and we are planning to do this
太好了，我们正计划这样做
at some point to provide some
在某个时候提供一些
visualization of these two stream
这两个流的可视化
processing graphs and they'll say
处理图，他们会说
interesting community project by Tim
蒂姆的有趣的社区项目
hope you can have a look at it I I found
希望你可以看看它II发现
it really awesome so you can have a look
真的很棒，所以你可以看看
here's a bunch of links and I wanted to
这是一堆链接，我想
direct you to our home page which we can
将您定向到我们的主页，我们可以
get a bunch of free ebook ebooks if
获得一堆免费的电子书，如果
you're interested with that I think we
您对此感兴趣，我认为我们
have a little bit of time for questions
有一点时间来提问
so I'm not sure how we're gonna take a
所以我不确定我们要如何
question yeah wait Thank You Quinn rich
问题是，等等，谢谢奎因·富
ok cool yeah thank thank you for a
好的，是的，谢谢。
wonderful webinar and so so far I see
精彩的网络研讨会，到目前为止，我看到了
only just a few questions so I try to
只有几个问题，所以我尝试
read it the first one from Thomas do I
从托马斯读第一本书
understand correctly and that you don't
正确理解而你却不明白
have to manually specify the request of
必须手动指定
n back to the publisher yessir yeah does
n返回发布者，是的，是的
that the implementation or reactive
表示执行或反应
stream API
流API
now do that to ya okay so and the answer
现在这样做，对吧，答案
is depending in which API so in reactive
取决于哪个API是反应式的
streams if you don't request manually
流，如果您不手动请求
you won't get any elements so you do
你不会有任何元素，所以你会
have to do with manually in reactive
与手动反应有关
streams which is the reason why our
流，这就是为什么我们
costumes and other implementations are
服装和其他实现是
so useful because we provide these Rico
非常有用，因为我们提供了这些Rico
strategies and you don't have to care
策略，您不必在意
about this at all just provide buffer
关于这一切只是提供缓冲
space and in the case of account you can
空间，如果是帐户，您可以
provide a request strategy for example a
提供一个请求策略，例如
good good one with an a hi low water
高低水好人好人
mark so you will know your buffer size
标记，以便您知道缓冲区大小
and you give us a high and low water
你给我们高低的水
marks when you want to start requesting
要开始请求时标记
and stop requesting for example if if
并停止请求，如果
you reach a high water mark of elements
您达到了高水准的元素
so you have your buffer is 10 I high
所以你的缓冲区是10我高
water mark is for example 8 you will
水印是例如8
stop requesting so you can drain a
停止请求，这样您就可以耗尽
little bit and when you reach for low
一点点，当你达到低点
water mark you will start with
您将开始的水印
requesting again but this is done
再次请求，但已完成
transparent before you buy acha okay
透明，然后再购买就可以了
thanks canoed and another question I'm
谢谢独木舟和另一个问题我
not sure anything correctly with Steve
与史蒂夫不知道什么正确
I've read it I'm new to this programming
我读过它，我是这个程序设计的新手
I want to know if the program has a
我想知道程序是否有
capacity as Java well I believe the
作为Java的能力，我相信
question is about performance ah ok yeah
问题是关于表现啊，好耶
so performance-wise the last numbers
所以性能方面的最后一个数字
I've seen them or I'll probably say
我看过他们，或者我可能会说
something wrong now it's been a while
出问题了一段时间了
but akka in general is able to perform
但是akka通常可以执行
with 5 million operations per second
每秒5百万次操作
message cents per second and yeah a
消息分每秒，是的
stream so acha based so we are aiming to
流如此基础，所以我们的目标是
get at least to a few million per second
至少每秒达到几百万
so this usually is not the bottleneck of
所以这通常不是瓶颈
your application and we tend to be the
您的应用程序，我们往往是
fast on the faster side of things so I
在事情的更快方面快，所以我
wouldn't worry about performance ok
不用担心性能还可以
great ah the next question where can I
很好啊，下一个问题我在哪里可以
find this source code that you showed
找到您显示的此源代码
okay that's that's an easy one arm it's
好吧，那是一条简单的手臂
on github you go to acha acha and verse
在github上，您要去acha acha和verse
sources for the arca streams are
arca流的来源是
currently living on the branch released
目前居住在分公司发布
to free dash death I can write it in the
为了释放破折号死亡，我可以写在
response yeah okay and I think it'd be
回应是的，我想
great if we could share this white so so
太好了，如果我们可以分享这个白色
after the webinar yeah that's not Lee
在网络研讨会之后，那不是李
okay great um and um the next question
好的，很好，嗯，下一个问题
oh I like it because I i also had had
哦，我喜欢，因为我也曾经
this question Oh what are the best use
这个问题哦，最好的用途是什么
cases of using our co streams and now
使用我们的协同流的案例以及现在
when do you suggest now not to use it
您现在什么时候建议不要使用它
okay um hmm well so I sorry I I just
好吧嗯嗯，所以我很抱歉我只是
believe fairy not everyone is aware of
相信童话不是每个人都知道的
acha and probably it would be great to
阿查，可能会很棒
cover now give her some examples on the
封面现在给她一些例子
use cases where stream soccer would be
使用流足球的用例
useful okay yeah gladly so let's start
有用，是的，很高兴，所以让我们开始吧
maybe not with occur in general so occur
也许不会与一般发生
in general is used when you need high
一般用于需要高
scalability because we have for example
可扩展性，因为例如
vaca cluster which means that because of
真空团簇，这意味着
how actors work they communicate only
演员如何工作，他们只交流
over messaging it is transparent to the
通过消息传递对它是透明的
user if this actor is on a remote on
用户，如果此演员位于远程
this cluster or another local system
该集群或其他本地系统
with me that means that you can scale
跟我一起意味着你可以扩展
out by just adding clusters and notes to
只需添加群集和注释即可
the cluster and the application doesn't
集群和应用程序不
really have to change much right because
真的必须做出很多改变，因为
it just will dispatch still messages and
它只会发送静止消息，
because the code doesn't change if it's
因为如果代码不变
local or remote you can just think about
您可以考虑的本地或远程
the concurrency in your system and not
系统中的并发
about ooh but now I have to scale out
关于哦，但现在我必须向外扩展
and it's going to be trouble annika we
这将是麻烦，Annika，我们
give you this location transparency so
为您提供此位置的透明度，因此
skating out is easy and also even
滑冰很容易，甚至
locally we tend to be really high
在本地，我们往往很高
performance practice at five million
500万的绩效实践
messages per second this usually is way
每秒的消息数通常是这样
higher than most
比大多数高
and then occur streams so on the
然后出现流，这样
downside of actavis in general is that
总的来说，Actavis的缺点是
they are very they can do anything right
他们非常可以做任何正确的事
and if we can do anything it comes at a
如果我们能做任何事情，它就会
cost it comes to the cost of complexity
涉及复杂性的代价
of following the code paths and with a
遵循代码路径并带有
curse dreams you have this precise path
诅咒梦想，你有这条精确的道路
how the elements are flowing in through
元素如何流过
this stream and what operations are
这个流以及什么操作是
being done on one so it's great for
在一个上完成，所以非常适合
these kinds of systems where you take
这类系统
some inputs need to transform it in a
一些输入需要将其转换为
bunch of ways and then signal it out to
一堆方法，然后发出信号
a bunch of other systems and or just to
一堆其他系统，或者仅仅是
a file so a mini MapReduce kind of
一个文件，所以像一个迷你MapReduce
things you can totally do this in memory
您可以完全在内存中完成的操作
with a car now I hope this answers your
带着车，我希望这能回答你
question oh and when when not to use
问题哦，什么时候不使用
yeah I think live here yeah it was also
是的，我想住在这里，也是
a part of question let's see when would
问题的一部分，让我们看看何时
you not use our car well like I said it
你不像我说的那样很好地使用我们的汽车
always comes performance cost
总会带来性能成本
performance costs on the complexity side
复杂性方面的性能成本
a little bit so if you have a problem
有点，所以如果你有问题
that is easily solvable with one fret
一品就可以轻松解决
and for processing is going to take five
而处理将需要五个
minutes on one hand maybe you don't need
几分钟，也许您不需要
a car on the other hand we do have very
另一方面，我们确实有
nice AP ice so you have to look at it
不错的AP冰，所以您必须看一下
and do the trade of comparison yeah okay
并进行比较交易是的，好吧
great our next question what if I need
伟大的下一个问题，如果我需要
to change the state of resource using
更改资源状态
feedback from a sink example Kafka's
来自接收器示例Kafka的反馈
worse depending on sink output rizzett
更糟，取决于接收器输出rizzett
kafka offset to an earlier offset it I'm
卡夫卡偏移到我之前的偏移量
trying to find the question so I can
试图找到问题，以便我可以
read it because it was bit complex it
阅读它，因为它有点复杂
from ever from Evan ah hi Evan
来自埃文ah hi Evan
I let me read it again slowly what if I
我让我慢慢读一遍，如果我
need to change the state of a swath
需要改变条带状态
using feedback from sync example cough
使用来自同步咳嗽的反馈
cosmos depending on sync output we set
宇宙取决于我们设置的同步输出
Kafka offset to an earlier so that's
卡夫卡偏移到更早，所以
like a that sounds like a replay or
听起来像是重播或
something like that that you need to
需要的东西
erase it the offset to something
消除它的偏移量
previous two to replay these values
前两个重播这些值
sounds like that to me so hello how I
对我来说听起来很像
would model this is and i have not shown
会模型这是，我没有显示
this today but we can do a graph a
今天，但我们可以做一个图
complexion graph and your graph would
肤色图，您的图会
have some feedback input and this would
有一些反馈输入，这将
be the feedback you can signal hey my
作为反馈，您可以发出信号，嘿，我的
sauce can you please go back a bit or
酱汁，请你再回一点
something so a source and i can be
这样的来源，我可以
inside a graph and then this graph can
在图里面，然后这个图可以
be as complex as you want it can have
尽可能地复杂
multiple in feedback inputs but then you
多个反馈输入，但随后您
can expose it to some other parts of
可以将其暴露于
just as a source so i think i would just
只是作为来源，所以我想我只是
model it as a graph and put the feedback
将其建模为图形并放入反馈
as a explicit input it doesn't have to
作为明确的输入，它不必
be back present for example hope this
回到现在例如希望这个
helps yeah okay so next question is good
可以，所以下一个问题很好
short message delivery guarantees and i
短信传递保证和我
believe it through its to their next
相信它，直到他们的下一个
question all to how error handling is
质疑所有错误处理方式
implemented in ARCA streams if one flow
如果一个流在ARCA流中实现
node fails we'll add a new to eventually
节点失败，我们将最终添加新的
know about that mm-hmm okay let's let's
知道了，嗯，让我们开始吧
also go at the same time so I'm message
也同时去，所以我发消息
delivery guarantees well currently this
交付目前很好保证
local so it isn't the same jvm so there
本地，所以它不是同一台JVM
is no message loss that powerfully
没有那么强大的消息丢失
answers the question so it's one radium
回答这个问题，所以是一个镭
so no network problems on the other hand
所以另一方面没有网络问题
I said we want to distribute this 2
我说过要散发这2
clusters eventually right so in fair we
集群最终正确，所以公平地说
will actually have to read
实际上将不得不阅读
implement redelivery with
实施与
acknowledgement we have internally for
内部确认
some system messages in arco so it's not
Arco中的一些系统消息，所以不是
an entirely new concept but it's
一个全新的概念，但是
something we have to expose to streams
我们必须向流公开的东西
for them to be able to read deliver
让他们能够阅读传递
messages and onwards to how error
消息及以后如何出错
handling is implemented so the way of
实现了处理方式
reactive streams to signal errors is
反应性流发出信号错误是
either by cancelling things or by what
通过取消事物或通过什么
that's actually the key methods by
这实际上是关键方法
signaling on error so when you have a
发信号通知错误，因此当您遇到
subscriber it has a bunch of methods
订户有很多方法
like on the next we've got the new
就像在下一个，我们有了新的
element on complete when the stream
流完成时元素
complete and finally on error and on
完成，最后出现错误
error get a frow bruh and this is how
错误弄皱了眉头，这是怎么回事
you pass around the failure of the
你绕过失败的
stream see would just tell you tell you
流见只会告诉你告诉你
subscribe of it yeah on error because of
因为错误而订阅它是的
something and if it has a downstream
什么东西，如果有下游
then it can propagate this error so
那么它可以传播这个错误，所以
directive streams wise like that and we
这样的指令流明智，我们
are still and thinking about because we
还在思考，因为我们
are running on top of a correct earth
在正确的地球上运行
and in our collectors we have a thing
在我们的收藏家中，我们有一件事
called a supervision hierarchy and the
称为监督等级制度，
supervision how he allows you to ya have
监督他如何让你拥有
someting failed resume if something
点东西失败恢复如果有的话
failed curvy entire thing and so we have
弯曲的整个东西都失败了，所以我们有
an ongoing discussion about that how to
关于如何进行的持续讨论
integrate able to move streams I can
整合能够移动流
just point you to the appropriate take
只是指出您合适的方法
it on github if you're interested we are
如果您有兴趣，请在github上找到它
definitely thinking about doing
绝对在考虑做
something more fancy okay thanks good
更花哨的东西好谢谢
the next question come are there any
下一个问题来了
plans for more predefined push-based
计划更多基于预定义的基于推的
sources like the time source for example
例如时间源
we source low in custom external
我们在定制外部提供低价
injection of elements although killer
虽然杀手注入元素
although they might not be quite in line
尽管他们可能不太符合
with relative streams
与相对流
too cool mm-hmm actually they are very
太酷了-嗯，实际上他们非常
quiet in line with the protocol and just
安静地遵守协议，只是
movie corvo's called sources and so
电影科尔沃的所谓来源
cannot really back pressure time that's
不能真正背压时间
basically what it means are you cannot
基本上这意味着你不能
really back pressure a guy clicking the
真的背了一个男人点击的压力
man's mouth like crazy and we're
男人的嘴像疯了似的，我们
protocol why's it still fits because you
协议为什么还适合，因为您
are allowed to drop elements right and
允许删除元素正确和
so for example the could be elements
因此，例如，可能是元素
which in in iraq's this one is called
在伊拉克的这个被称为
debounce so that means if i get a
去抖动，这意味着如果我得到一个
thousand clicks per second yeah don't
每秒千次点击是的
don't send all of these downstream but
不要将所有这些都发送到下游，但是
just send one in this one second and so
只需在此一秒钟内发送一个
was definitely support for that but we
绝对是对此的支持，但我们
don't have any built-in except for time
除了时间没有任何内置
source currently i think the focus is a
目前我认为重点是
bit more on the back ends currently
目前在后端多一点
we're such sources are can be avoided
我们这样的来源是可以避免的
and tcp doesn't really count we have a
tcp并没有真正算出我们有一个
tcp source of course which we use for
我们当然使用的tcp来源
our HTTP and I bio and but it's a bit
我们的HTTP和我的简历，但这有点
different because the operating system
不同，因为操作系统
also has a TCP buffer and we are kind of
也有一个TCP缓冲区，我们有点
reliant additionally on the TCP buffer
额外依赖于TCP缓冲区
in the operating system um so that's
在操作系统中，所以
fast actually other plans for yeah i
快速的其他计划，是的，我
think this answers the question we are
认为这回答了我们的问题
looking into what kind of sources we can
研究我们可以提供什么样的资源
provide and we don't really have much
提供，我们真的没有太多
push based ones okay great and probably
基于推送的，还不错，可能
the last question how well do archive
最后一个问题存档的效果如何
streams integrate with an existing aqua
溪流与现有的水相融合
cluster application as i understand it
据我了解，集群应用程序
currently creates a known actor system
当前创建一个已知的演员系统
okay so let's first let's start with the
好吧，让我们首先开始
misconception the misconception here is
误解这里的误解是
vetted creating on after system it does
审核在系统完成后创建
not really have to create an allnighter
真的不必创建一个通宵
system so if you have an existing
系统，如果您已有
application you can use your existing
您可以使用现有的应用程序
actor system what you will need
演员系统您将需要什么
to create the flow materializer but this
创建流物化器，但这
is only an object that takes care of a
只是一个照顾一个对象
materialization it is not additional
实现不是额外的
threat boot so when reuse existing
威胁启动，因此当重用现有设备时
infrastructure in lab and how well would
实验室的基础设施以及性能如何
it integrative cluster well cluster
一体化集群集群
however will it integrate with actors on
但是它将与演员整合
the remote nodes I would ask because
我会问的远程节点，因为
verse 4 key problem to solve we are not
第4节要解决的关键问题我们不是
very yet so i won't really be a pulling
非常，所以我真的不会被吸引
rabbits out of my head how how it will
兔子从我的头上跳出来怎么回事
look like but we would really like to
看起来，但我们真的很想
implement this okay okay cool I think
实现这个好吧好吧酷我认为
that's that's all we got and we covered
这就是我们所拥有的，我们涵盖了
pretty much everything um well again
几乎一切都很好
thank you can wait for your great
谢谢你可以等你的伟大
presentation and we'll be sharing slides
演示文稿，我们将共享幻灯片
in a blog no um I think that's it yeah
在博客中，我认为就是这样
updates every 13 time yeah take care bye
每13次更新一次，请注意再见
have a good day luton
祝你有美好的一天